Narrator: 1
Speaker 1: What’s your address?
Speaker 2: Two hundred and thirteen Station Road.
Narrator: 2
Speaker 1: When’s your birthday?
Speaker 2: The twentieth of June.
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: So how many people live here?
Speaker 2: About a hundred and twenty thousand, I think.
Narrator: 4
Speaker 1: How much did the house cost?
Speaker 2: A lot.
Seven hundred and ninety-five thousand.
Speaker 1: Is that in pounds or dollars?
Speaker 2: Dollars.
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: How much of your salary do you spend on rent?
Speaker 2: Er, at least a third, I think.
Narrator: 6
Speaker 1: What percentage of your day do you spend working or studying?
Speaker 2: I’m not sure.
Between sixty and seventy per cent, maybe?